freelightroompresets.co 2018-09-08

# Privacy Policy - FREE LIGHTROOM PRESETS - 27 FREE PRESETS

FREE-LIGHTROOM-PRESETS.CO

FREE-LIGHTROOM-PRESETS.CO takes the protection of your privacy very seriously. Your personal data will be only stored on this site in technically required extent. The data will not – in any case – be passed on or will be sold to third parties. By entering or using FREE-LIGHTROOM-PRESETS.CO you agree to this rules. You have the right to object to any usage of your data. You can withdraw your consent to this policy at any time with effect for the future. This privacy policy refers to our site and does not apply for third party sites, to which we refer or link.

The following statement gives an overview of how we ensure this protection, what type of data is collected and for what purpose.

1\. Collection and use of personal data

FREE-LIGHTROOM-PRESETS.CO automatically collects and stores with every use of FREE-LIGHTROOM-PRESETS.CO in our server log files information that your browser sends to us when you use our Internet service. Browser type, date and time of each action are included in this information. We store this data in order to provide our services to you and to undertake analysis to improve and develop them. A compilation of these data with registration information will not be made, therefore personal exploitation will not happen. The data will be deleted after the statistical analysis.

2\. Communication of personal data to third parties

FREE-LIGHTROOM-PRESETS.CO collects and uses only the data that you provide to us when using our website. Your information is kept confidential. Basically, we do not give your personal data to any third parties. We do not communicate your personal data without your permission with any third parties.

3\. Data Protection

We encrypt your personal information via the Internet, using the so-called SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) method. Nevertheless, the provision of personal data, whether in person, or over the Internet, always involves risks, and no system of technology is completely secure against manipulation or sabotage. FREE-LIGHTROOM-PRESETS.CO takes within reason precautions to prevent unauthorized access to your personal data and the unauthorized use or falsification of data and to minimize possible risks.

4\. Cookies

The webpage of FREE-LIGHTROOM-PRESETS.CO uses in several places so-called cookies. They serve to make our service more user-friendly, effective and secure. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer by your browser. Most of the cookies we use are so-called “session cookies”. They will be deleted automatically after the end of the session. The use of cookies is an industry standard and many web sites use them. Cookies are stored on your computer and not on this page. Cookies do no harm your computer and do not contain viruses. We only use cookies to read information on your hard drive, that have been stored there by a cookie from this page. In case you don’t want the storage of cookies on your computer or want to get notified about their usage, you can adjust the settings of your browser, if it allows you to.

5\. Sign Up & Newsletter

As soon as you sign up as a member you’ll automatically receive our newsletter. No further information will be collected. You can withdraw your consent to your data storage, your email address and their exploitation to send you the newsletter at any time. If you don’t want to receive FREE-LIGHTROOM-PRESETS.CO’s Newsletter anymore please send us an Email to thnx@freelightroompresets.co using the subject “unsubscribe” or unsubscribe [here](http://freelightroompresets.us3.list-manage1.com/unsubscribe?u=16d22e96360b2616928f5cb15&id=ec46307ff2 "Unsubscribe").

6\. Your Account

You can delete your account at any time. For this please write us a short notification, including either your username or Email Address, to thnx@freelightroompresets.co. We will delete your account and your personal data and send you a confirmation.

7\. Changes

FREE-LIGHTROOM-PRESETS.CO can change at any time – and without notice – this privacy policy, the content of the page or can change or block the access to this page. We therefore recommend reading these terms each time when visiting the website, so that you know at any time, for what purposes we use your data.

8\. Inquiry right

You always have the right to get information regarding the recording of your personal data, its origin and destination and the purpose of storage. Information can be obtained by writing an Email to thnx@freelightroompresets.co.

9\. Further information

Your trust is important to us. We will answer your questions concerning your personal data at any time. If you have questions that cannot be answered by the privacy policy provided by us or you want to investigate further on a certain topic, feel free to contact us at any time.

This Privacy Policy have been modified on February, 24 2015.
